

Last 10 years I work on cable television system company.

Make web applications for helping employees. For example customers list. Google Firebase is used as backend. Github pages is used for client app hosting.

Now looking for apply a frontend developer with React or Angular.

CONTACT

PHONE: +375 29 313 65 78

WEBSITE: CV online

EMAIL:

zmichgen@gmail.com

GITHUB:

https://github.com/zmichgen

MIKHAIL ZYRANAU

Junior(+) Frontend Developer

EDUCATION

Rolling Scopes School, Minsk, Belarus

09.2018 – 03.2019 Frontend development course. Frontend developer.

Higher State College of Telecommunication, Minsk< Belarus

1998 - 2001

Radio and Television broadcasting. Engineer of communication.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Rolling Scopes School, Trainee

10.2008 - 02.2009

Created several projects, using HTML, SCSS, Webpack, Javascript, React, Angular 7, Github, Heroku, Firebase, Nodejs, Express, MongoDB Live portfolio available at Github ...

MAGOTEL, Engineer of communication

2009 - Present

Created customer list, equipment list, using c#, Angular, JQuery, HTML, CSS. Portfolio don't available because it's only for internal use.

SKILLS

Tools: VSCode, Postman, ChromeDevTool, Photoshop... **Tech:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, MySQL, React, Angular...

You may see more in my online CV